We're together, together, together. I love you. Cute.
So cute, so cute, so cute
So cute, so cute, I can't stop, love, love
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
So cute, so cute, so cute
Cute, cute, cute Kiss Kiss for all of it
I can forgive anything... everything is so cute... kiss kiss kiss... everything is so cute... I can forgive anything
It's a sin to be cute.
Matching key ring and duplicate key.
Every day is an anniversary.
I'm not going to let you know who's calling you.
It's not cute to be mean.
You're lying, aren't you?
You love me
You're so cute, so cute, so cute!
You love me, you love me, you love me, you love me, you love me, you love me
Don't make me nervous.
I love you too much, I love you so much, I hate you so much, I love you so much
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, ME.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, me.
me
me.
I'll never let go of you.
You don't have to tell me. I know.
Why didn't you give me a better hug today before bedtime?
Why can't you give me a better hug?
I don't know.
I'm so irrationally mad at you.
Don't hate me.
It's hard to be in love.
I love you so much.
Sometimes I'm indifferent.
Don't be bothered.
Please accept it.
Ah.
So cute!
So cute, so cute, so cute!
Cute, cute, cute, I can't stop Love & Me
I'm so cute, so cute, so cute
I've got you all to myself
So cute
Cute, cute, too cute
Cute, cute, cute Kiss me for all of it
I can't forgive anything, it's so cute I can't forgive anything, kiss kiss kiss
It's a sin to be cute
If you like it, it's a sin
Cute, isn't it? See you on FM924, AM1422, Radio Japan, sunny and sometimes super hot!
Good evening, everyone.
Radio Nippon Saturdays at 1:00 a.m.
Speaking of...
Harometekitateki Cho-tokimeki Channel
Yes, this is the second show to be released.
Today's Harutoki MC is,
Yes, I'm Kanami Tojinokanami, a.k.a. Kanamin, the super-tokimeki blue.
Today's member is,
Yes, Anjulia, a.k.a. Juli, from Super Tokimeki Purple,
Hitoka Sakai, a.k.a. Hito-chan, a.k.a. Hitoka, a.k.a. Hito-chan, a.k.a. Hitokimeki Red,
Yes, Haruka Koizumi, a.k.a. Oharu, a.k.a. Super Thrilling Pink,
Yes, with Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu of Super Tokimeki Lemon, and Aki Suda, aka Aki-chan of Super Tokimeki Lemon,
Hi, I'm Hiyorin from Super Tokimeki Green.
I'm Hiyori Hayashi from Super Tokimeki Green.
Hi, I'm Hiyorin.
Yes, I'm Hiyorin.
So all six of us will be present for this open recording.
Yay!
I don't know how to end this, because I've been saying "toot, toot, toot.
And that's it.
Only Uru-chan can't say her full name.
I was Hiyorin.
I didn't know what it was.
I'm Jessica Hiyori.
Congratulations.
So, today's show is being streamed live on YouTube,
It's being streamed live on YouTube.
Yoo-hoo.
Yoo-hoo!
Are you watching?
It's Wednesday, right?
Yoo-hoo-hoo.
Yes, yes, Wednesday, Wednesday.
Thank you very much.
Hello.
Please send me lots of comments.
I'll be waiting for you in the chat room.
I'll be waiting for you.
I have a question I'd like to ask you,
Are you listening to me?
Are you listening?
Thank you very much.
Do you usually listen too, Liz? Springtime.
Yes, I do.
It's played a lot at my house too.
But my mom listens to my family.
Hiyori, my mom picks me up in the car on the way home,
When I get in the car, it's playing.
It's on Bluetooth, so it echoes throughout the car.
It's really embarrassing.
It's a little embarrassing, isn't it?
I understand.
My voice.
Yes, I do.
So, I would like to enjoy talking with you today,
Let's enjoy talking together until the end.
Let's have fun together until the end.
This is fresh, isn't it?
It's really fresh.
It really is.
I'm glad. It's a little different when there's this kind of applause. It's different from usual.
When we are recording a radio show, we throw a lot of things at each other and talk together,
But you can't get the real voices or reactions of the audience right away.
That's true.
I'm a little happy today.
Please give me a lot of reactions.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's have fun.
Our seats.
Here we are.
Well, let's sit down, shall we?
This is starting to sound like a press conference.
Yeah, it looks a little layered.
Hey.
Thank you very much.
Yes, the radio show is about to start.
Yes, that's right, every Saturday at 1:00 a.m. for 30 minutes on Radio Japan, which is celebrating its 65th anniversary of opening its legs.
Sunny Time, ah, Sunny Time Super Tokimeki Advertising Club, this program started in April of 2017.
This will be the first public recording in five years.
It's been five years.
It's your first time, right?
It's Aki-chan's first time.
Today is the first public recording.
How did you like it?
It's a little strange to think that my voice is going to be on the radio.
It's like a live performance where I talk all the time.
That's for sure.
So this time, I'm going to be talking from Radiant Hall in Yokohama for about 40 minutes.
Yes, please.
By the way, when was the last time all six members of the spring season gathered together?
It has been since January, the end of the year and the beginning of the new year.
It's the first time since the 300th anniversary in January that all six of us have been together.
We usually record radio programs with three or two members,
It's a little bit new for us to be together.
The first time we did a radio show was with the six of us,
And then we, me and Hiorin,
And then we, me, Hiorin, and one other person will call in remotely,
And then we, me, Hiorin, and one other person will call in remotely, or video call in, and do the radio show?
I don't know,
And then..,
Pio,
Petit case?
You know, the one you forgot?
What? Was it then?
That was the first time?
I don't know. I was taking a bath.
You know, like that.
Pokey doesn't know.
It's one of the most embarrassing moments of the show.
The manager was really pissed at me.
Yes, I was.
There was a time when that happened.
Yes, it did. I'm glad.
The last time we did a public recording.
I think we did a lot of live music.
About four songs.
Outside.
It's a very faint memory.
The wind was howling.
I know... but... was the script in view? - Yes, it was! - Yes, yes! Was it like... the script was like...
- I had an image of it!
- I knew I had an image of it!
- I knew it!
- I don't remember that at all.
- I don't remember it at all. It was like, when we went to the tent in the machine room, it was like, "Boom, boom, boom, boom!
- Do you remember the tent in the machine room?
- I remember. I remember. I remember it. I think it's going to fly away.
I remember.
This time it's indoors.
That's right.
Don't worry about that.
It's safe.
It's safe and sound.
But isn't it too hot? It's kind of...
Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
It's hot.
Hot.
I like it hot.
Do you want to get some air conditioning?
You want to find out what the temperature is?
I'd like to hear what you guys think. In person.
In the room time. Staff, please.
Also, also, also, today is an important day.
Yes, today, September 27, is the release date of the lovely Memorial.
Thank you very much.
It's a very important day, but thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
It's a very important day,
I hope you all have seen the music video,
Have you seen it?
Did you see it?
Thank you very much.
I hope you all saw it.
I'm so glad.
You were so cute.
We shot it in Indonesia,
It had a very Indonesian feel to it.
It wasn't Japan.
It was just a different place to shoot.
It's just a different place.
In a good way.
It feels grand.
And the coupling song
The coupling song has been released.
I wonder if you listened to it.
"You and Youth" was playing earlier.
Did you listen to it?
We recorded it a little while ago.
A little while ago.
That was the first time...
You know, the first time we choreographed the song?
I did, with an A.
Really?
Yeah, last time we recorded it.
Pio and Kanami.
Who was it? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I've decided!
I didn't get it until just now.
I'll be right back.
I don't know...
yes
Awww...
This time...
It's not just the music video.
It's not just the music video, it's the teaser.
And dance practices...
There's a lot of music videos and dance practices...
I don't know.
And on TikTok.
They're dancing on TikTok.
That's right.
I've seen people making videos of their favorites.
And you see them making guess videos.
It's nice.
It's so exciting.
We always live together a little bit at a time, a little bit at a time, watching the videos you made in the past.
Little by little...
It's coming little by little.
And you know what?
They made a cute memorial effect on TikTok, guys!
Yeah!
We just did that.
You guys don't know about it, do you? Not yet.
It's like a game and it's fun, so please try it, Himina, play with it!
Try it. Hearts are falling.
Catch them?
Ten hearts?
Like the one Julia was into.
Julia used to play like this for a while.
It's a very easy pattern. It's pretty gentle.
It's pretty gentle, so I thought a lot of people could clear it.
I thought maybe I could clear it for the first time, but for the first time, oh, there were people who couldn't clear it.
One time, pretty much.
What's that?
I'm pretty sure I thought I could clear it, too.
I thought I could clear it.
I was saying, "I thought I could clear it," and it was like game over.
Game over.
Is there such a pattern?
There is such a thing as game over.
You scared me.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
But when I did it for the first time, my chin was a little squished.
It's hard to make it look cute, isn't it?
It's difficult.
But it's pretty fun.
Please give it a try.
I'd love to see you try it. So, can we leave it at that?
Shall we go?
Okay?
Okay? Okay? Can we go? Can I tell you? Can I say it? Can I?
Can I say it now?
Can I?
I'm going to do that corner that I've been wanting to do in the open recording,
I'd like to do that corner that I wanted to do in the open recording,
But before that, I would like to sing one more song,
I would like to sing one more song before that, so I would like you to open the floor for me again.
Let's get our hands ready.
So, I'd like to talk about today's breakfast.
I'd like to talk about your breakfast today. Did you eat breakfast today?
You didn't eat? You didn't eat?
So I'll talk about lunch.
You haven't eaten?
By the way, those who ate...
I ate today. I ate today.
I'm unhealthy.
But it's just in time. I guess it was just in time.
What did I eat?
Junior? Junior had a very rare breakfast today.
For the first time in about a year, Mom got him a McDonald's. McGriddles?
Oh! Isn't that good? It's so good! Do you use them?
That sweet bun with a little bread...I don't know how to call it. I don't know how to say it...it's like sweet and salty.
Yes, it was a morning-only thing, like a hamburger, and I was so happy.
Yes, it had been a very long time.
It was delicious.
Kanamin, did you have negitoro-don?
Oh, there it is!
It's out! I really did eat it last night, but yesterday I had it rolled up with negitoro and ate the leftover negitoro as negitoro donburi in the morning.
It was delicious.
How about you, Oharu?
Oharu had soba noodles.
Soba and cod roe on rice.
The usual tension.
I hear that from time to time.
I ate sweet potatoes.
Oh!
That's what I'm talking about!
It's a little unhealthy, but I bought it at a convenience store and ate a sweet potato.
Eeyan.
Hiyori, udon.
Udon!
Udon sounds good.
Udon with sudachi?
Sudachi?
Sudachi.
First, Atafu-san gave me this.
Very sudachi udon?
Well, I thought I'd ask him about lunch and then we'll go to the song.
Are you sure?
I had 20 minutes before I came today.
About 25 minutes.
And I really wanted to eat sushi.
So I went to a sushi restaurant, ate in 15 minutes, and left.
Wow, that's amazing.
What are you talking about? Because I really wanted to eat it and I couldn't resist.
So I'll do my best today.
Okay, so...
Now I'd like to go to the next song.
Please listen.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I'm already sweating.
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
I can't stop.
Oh no.
My stomach will stop. I won't stop, I won't stop.
The version that stops
Okay, so...
Here is something that made me happy recently.
Oh, no.
Do you have any? Something that made you happy?
You all had them. I was happy today.
Moments that made you excited.
You had about three of them.
Which ones?
I'm going to say all of them. The moment when you got excited. It happened three times before, didn't it? Which one do you want?
Say it quickly.
You're going to say them all?
Okay, let's start with the first one.
Okay.
Employee Muscat!
And they're not just employee muscats.
That's right.
It's in a box with a room full of employee muscats, one by one.
Isn't that amazing? I've never seen anything like it.
It's jewelry.
Yes, it is.
Sparkling.
That was amazing.
It was sparkling. You were shining.
Shine shine.
You're good.
There were grapes in it, right?
Yes, yes.
And alternating grapes.
There were two boxes.
Yes, there were two boxes.
We were doing a tour until a little while ago,
There was a chance to win a raffle, and only the winners would get a yakiniku bento or something like that,
So the other day at the final show, I drew the lottery,
So at the final show the other day, I drew a lottery and was told I would get an exciting gift.
And there was one member who didn't win,
What?
It was a favor from the staff,
Yes, that's right.
There were a lot of employee muscats in the box.
They got a good award, right?
There was a rotation of them,
Hiorin's?
Well, during the promotion,
I'm sure you got a lot of looks during the promotion.
I got the "Hiorin's".
I thought, "Is that really necessary? I was wondering...
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you're right, I mean, I'm sure Oharu and...
I mean, when Oharu and Julia were doing the promotion...
I was just doing this.
But it turned into a show.
I'm glad we did it.
There was a sense of perspective, wasn't there?
There was a sense of perspective.
Really kind staff.
Gentle love.
Thank you very much.
Shall we go back to our seats?
Yes.
It's really hot.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
It's so hot that I feel like I'm outside.
But maybe it's cooler outside now.
That's for sure.
It's getting a lot cooler these days. It's already cold at night. But maybe it's cooler outside now. Indeed. Indeed. It's getting a lot cooler these days.
Yes, it's cold at night.
I'm happy.
It's cold.
But you know what? If I keep talking about this,
Aki-chan and Pew's summer vs. winter battle will start,
Bekki bekki.
Okay, I'll go. Okay, I'll go on then.
Yes, please.
65th anniversary of the opening of the legs.
Eh~ sorry, one more time.
FM924, AM1422
Radio Japan
Halley! Doki Doki! JR!
Kanamin! Kanamin! Julia!
Hito-chan! Oharu! Kiyoshi Susuda and Hiyori Kawa
Today...
Why can't you two shake it?
Just the two of course.
And we got hung.
I'm sorry.
Hung?
Hung.
I don't mind that it's only four letters.
It's only four letters. It's like seven letters, but it's four letters.
I got greedy.
Let's be greedy.
Sorry. I got greedy. Let's be greedy. Yes, let's be greedy.
So today, all six of us are gathered here at Yokohama Radiant Hall for the second open recording of this program.
Okay. Now, after this, I would like to show you that corner.
I would like to have a big round of applause after my title call,
Please give a big round of applause, everyone.
Are you ready?
OK!
Okay, everyone, let's go.
Let's start from here,
Kanami's Ganba!
Yeah!
That's great!
Thank you very much.
Yes, this corner is for the listeners' problems,
This corner is a place where all the members, with Kana-bin at the center, try to solve your problems.
I'm so happy. I'm so happy to be able to do this corner in such an open recording.
Thank you very much.
Well, it is like Kanabin's corner,
It's like a corner for everyone.
I see.
Well then, let's get started.
This time, we have asked all of the publicists who came to the venue to fill out a questionnaire in advance,
So I would like to proceed with the corner based on the answers.
I would like to proceed based on the answers to the questionnaire.
Okay, I will read it.
I will now read them.
This is HARUTOKI Neem, from Himeka.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to take a bath...
It takes me so long to take a bath,
It takes me more than an hour to get in.
How can I go home early? So, I sympathize with you.
Julia also sympathizes.
But, isn't Hiyori early?
I don't hesitate at all.
That's great.
He is really fast.
When we were in the same room at the hotel.
Hiyori says, "I'm going to take a bath.
Almost as soon as she entered the room.
Because, you know, the first time you do something you don't like...
No, I love baths.
It's not that I don't like it.
But if you let her take a bath first...
It's easier later.
I understand that.
Because, you know, when I'm on an expedition, I'm with Pio.
Each of us is usually alone in our room.
We go in the room.
I take off my clothes within 10 seconds.
Wow.
That's amazing.
That's too good.
You'll never get in there.
I'll get sloppy.
That's it... the moment you think about going in...
I think I should just take off my clothes. I see.
That's what I really think.
I'll take off my clothes.
But I have an image of you being the slowest to take a bath in the war,
What?
Julia.
What? Julia?
Definitely Julia.
From what I hear, it's pretty much Julia.
Yes, I've heard a lot about her.
I think it's Aki-chan. I think it's Aki-chan, too. From what I hear, it's pretty much Julian. That's right.
I think I am Aki-chan.
I think it's Aki-chan, too.
Ah.
If I were alone, I could do my best.
If I were alone, I would be in a hurry because there would be no one to wake me up the next day,
But I would be able to relax for a couple of hours.
Yes, that's right.
It flows.
We can watch a movie.
Yes, that's right.
And with Aki-chan, I can't take a bath anymore.
Ha-ha-ha!
That's right!
Are you sure? Can I tell you that already?
What? You're okay with that?
Then we'll get you a room.
You mean you don't want to be with me?
Wait! If I share a room with Akichan, we'll probably have to wake up in the morning together.
That happened once before, didn't it?
Yes, twice.
Yes, it happened twice.
The big graduation day.
Yes, and then there was another day.
Another day.
It was in the morning.
Yeah, we just... we just chatted.
We chatted till about 5:00.
We found ourselves in the same room.
But Aki-chan was taking a bath at that time.
That's right.
Even when she didn't.
What? Even when she wasn't.
She was taking a bath during the incident that everyone knows about.
I was in it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
We have to support them.
Yes, yes. You shouldn't sympathize.
That's right.
I failed.
Yeah, yeah.
What was that? It's something,
Stock up on your favorite bath salts,
And they'll come out of the inside. Stock up on your favorite bath salts. Sure.
They come out from the inside.
Figurines and so on.
Yes, yes.
Why don't you make a special selection?
Goods?
Goods. Sasbombs?
Seven kinds of bath salts with characters coming out from the inside.
So cute!
With Pavlin,
Pavlin and..,
You know what?
I want to make a figure version of that one, too. I want to make a figure version of that.
Just the face is cute.
I like it!
Then I can't wait to release it.
Bath bombs.
Isn't this good?
It's pretty good.
I want one.
It's perfect for the coming season.
Let's make some goods. Yay! There aren't too many idols who put out bath bombs. Idols who make bath bombs.
No one does.
It's pretty good, isn't it?
It's definitely cute.
It's consumable.
They're consumable.
We can keep it inside.
I'll let you work on that.
I don't know if we can get it out with that, but we'll try our best to get it out. Let's have them do their best. I don't know if we can get it out with that, but I will try my best to get it out.
I will try my best.
So I think it would be a good idea to make some fun with bath salts or something and take a bath early.
Yes, I will.
Then, let's all do our best so that Himeka can take a bath.
I'll deliver it to you.
Okay, I'm going.
Here we go. Ready.
Oh, sorry.
If I said Himeka..,
Oh, okay.
OK, OK.
I'll tell you my name first.
I'm ready to go.
Ready? Himeka.
Se-no.
Gamburn!
Yes. Well, I still want to go. I'm looking forward to it. You can read a lot. It's fun. Then, I would like to go next.
I'm looking forward to it.
I can read a lot.
Then, I'll read next time.
Then I'll read it.
This is from Haretoki Name, You are Advertising Department member.
Thank you very much.
I wanted to have a new hobby, so I started studying for the Level 1 government certification last week.
It's so hard to study so much as an adult,
I know you guys remember a lot of lyrics and dances,
Do you have any tips? I am wondering if you have any tips.
Thank you very much.
First grade in the order of relationship is amazing.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's difficult. It's difficult.
I can't remember it at all.
I think it would be good if two people who are fast at learning choreography and dance could answer this question.
Certainly.
Juliakie.
Am I fast?
Ah, well...
How about you?
Well, I guess...
The trick to learning is...
In Jillia's case...
Movement...
That's what it's about.
I've only got up to the second level of Giglia,
If it's a movement that reminds me of something, I pull something here, yes, I always think about it by attaching something else to the movement in my mind,
If it was a movement, I would always have something else attached to the movement in my head, like this feeling is like this, or if it was a movement, I would say, yes, this movement is like this, then this movement is like this, left to right, yes, round and round, round and round.
I was already trying to connect it to something in my head,
I can learn it in the moment when I am trying to connect it with something,
So I try to use my head.
I often compare it to something when I'm trying to remember something.
That's great advice.
Advice that shows how smart you are.
Hey...
I don't know.
Is that enough?
Now that's some advice.
I don't know.
I've been practicing typing lately.
Ooh.
Just keep at it, just keep at it, and do your best to keep the sushi flowing.
Ah.
Sushi practice.
I've been practicing hard and typing fast.
I do it all the time when I have free time.
So, so,
If you have free time, look at the kanji,
And if you have free time, you should look at Kanji characters.
If you have free time, you should look at Kanji characters, and if you have free time, you should look at Kanji characters.
Busy time, yes.
That's for sure.
If you repeat it over and over again, you will learn it.
It's important, isn't it? Repeat.
We also talked about backstage work many times to make sure we were all on the same page.
Before the performance, we would all say, "Let's do it.
If it's today...
Se-no.
I love it!
Oh, I made a mistake. I made a mistake. If it were today, I'd say, "Se-no, I like you!
Oh, I made a mistake.
I made a mistake.
Is it just sudden?
Yeah.
Sorry, sorry.
So, MC Asa-san, my song.
He said, "Se-no, kawaii memorial!
I was like, "Was it 23 on that tour?
I was doing about 2 or 3 or 2 songs.
I did about 2 songs.
Before the show, we had to start from the beginning.
We made sure that we all said it from the beginning before the show.
If it was a kanji, we would write a lot of kanji.
You know, like saying it.
It's important, isn't it?
I think it's important, so let's repeat it.
Let's do our best!
I know it's hard, but repetition is the key.
Cheer and cheer!
But I'm rooting for you, so keep up the good work!
Bye,
I would like to give a shout out to YUA and YUA at Advertising staff!
YUA at Advertising staff, let's go!
I'll do my best!
Go for it!
Yes! And I would like to go one more.
Let's go.
Okay, do you want me to read it?
Please do.
Haretoki name, it's from Hoshijin. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I am a trainer of young employees at work. What kind of talk is OK for your generation to grab?
What employee?
What did you say?
I'm an educator,
An educator.
What kind of talk does your generation need to get a grip?
Blue.
That means you're a kid from our generation, right?
Yes, the great new kids.
What kind of talk?
Grabbing?
I wonder.
You mean a talk that's going to be fun.
Yeah.
What's the catch?
Talking about what's hot?
me
Me.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
Pretty, pretty, pretty, I love you.
Pretty, pretty, pretty. Kiss, kiss, kiss all of it.
I can forgive anything
It's a crime to be cute.
Matching keys, matching key chains.
Every day is an anniversary.
Who's calling me? I'm not sure, but you should answer.
It's not cute to be mean.
You're lying, aren't you?
You love me
That's so cute!
So cute! So cute! So cute!
You're so cute. You're so cute. I can't stop smiling at you.
You're making me nervous, meme.
Me. Me.
Me.
me.
me
I can't stop loving me, loving me, loving me, hating me, hating me, hating me, hating me.
Oh, my God, it's not true. I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love.
I love you. I love you. I'll never let you go.
What about you?
You don't have to tell me. I know.
Why can't you give me more hugs today before bedtime?
Why can't you give me a better hug?
I don't know anymore.
I'm so irrationally mad at you.
Don't hate me.
It's hard to love someone.
I love you so much.
I get mad sometimes.
Don't be a pain in the ass.
Please accept it.
Ah.
Cute!
Cute, cute, cute, I love it
Cute, cute, cute I can't stop, love, love
Hey, I'm beautiful.
I got you all to myself
Cute. Cute. Cute.
Cute. Cute. Cute. I love it.
Pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty.
Kiss me
You can't forgive anything, can you?
It's a sin to be cute.
I like it.
Meme.
meme
me
mememe
me me me me me
Don't change, don't stop
Oh, how I wish again
I believe in the time I have with you
That's why I know
I'm the universe of love I'm the one who's looking out for you
I'm the one you should be looking at
I'm always...
I'm always lost, aren't I?
Now it's my turn.
Five, five, five, five, we're together
Dream, dream, dream
Dream on, dream on, dream on
Gum cella's every day has meaning... meme
me
me me me
I'm full of meme That's why I chose you and youth
No matter how many times I make it come true, the dream that never ends
I want to make it come true, I want to make it come true
A shooting star in the distance
With this heart, we'll run through with our dreams
It won't change, it won't change, as long as there's excitement in my heart
Chasing the future forever, embracing the reasons we can't give up
I believe in the time I have with you
I'll keep running with you from now on You and youth are Wow...
More, more, more, a little more me
Please don't make me burn, don't be a softy, I want to keep that kind smile all to myself, so I'm going to Nagi, but please don't make me hurry, this world.
Yes, yes, yes...
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
Suddenly
Kaikyoku 65th Anniversary FM924 AM1422 Radio Japan
Hare, Tokidoki Cho Tokimeki Cho Tokimeki Propaganda Club!
It's time for the ending of the open recording session with all six of us together.
Now, here is an announcement from the Chotokimeki Advertising Department.
Yes, so today, today, a cute memorial went on sale.
Yay!
There it is! It's here!
Thank you very much.
I'm sure everyone has already gotten the CDs and so on,
Please enjoy watching and listening to it.
And next year, 2024,
4 years!
January 27 and 28 at Yokohama Arena,
We will be performing live in Yokohama Arena on January 27th and 28th.
Please come and visit us.
Also, the day after tomorrow, we are going to have a release event at LAZONA Kawasaki,
We are going to have the release event at LAZONA Kawasaki.
Is it close to here?
Not so close.
But is it the same?
I'm in Yokohama, but Kawasaki.
Not too far.
We are in the same Kanagawa prefecture.
Please come. We are looking forward to seeing you.
[Applause] So, the first public recording in five years, which was sent from Yokohama Radiant Hall on the day of the release of the new song, is coming to an end next time.
What a great way to end our first public recording in five years, but now it's time for the next one.
Well, let me tell you one by one what I think of today, and I would like to start with you.
Thank you all for coming to see me today, even though it was a weekday.
The members and I have been talking about doing a public recording of Radio Japan for a long time, and now that it's actually happening, I'm really happy that we were able to have such a good time together.
I'm so happy that we could actually make it happen and have a good time with everyone!
And today, we successfully released a cute memorial album!
We have released many CDs, and each time they are full of great songs, so it's not a matter of course that we can release a CD like this.
I'll be happy if I can develop each song together with you all and make it into a song that people can get excited about at live performances.
So thank you all very much for coming to see me today.
Yes, thank you to everyone who came to see me today, and thank you to everyone who is listening, and thank you to everyone for the streaming.
Well, as KANOMI said, today is the release day of "Cute Memorial",
I'm really happy to be able to meet you all on the day of release and to be able to record the spring time,
I am very happy that we were able to celebrate this day without any problems.
I think that on the day of the release, we usually deliver the songs, read the comments, and have a conversation with the audience,
How did you feel about this slightly different atmosphere?
How was it to be able to sing the song live and actually perform the cute memorial song on the day of the live?
Long time?
Long?
I'm about to talk about it when I see your impressions after the show.
I'll try to keep it short.
I was really happy,
Also, it's thanks to everyone's support that we were able to release this cute memorial album.
Thank you very much.
I am also looking forward to the offline Taku Exhibition starting this month, which will give me a chance to meet many of you.
I hope you all will continue to love these lovely memorials.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Yes, thank you very much for today.
So, to all of you who came to see me today, and to those of you who are watching the video, which one of you is it?
Thank you very much.
Yes, it's been a long time since I've done a public recording, but it felt fresh and fun to talk in front of everyone like this.
We started this haaretoki quite some time ago, and we have been doing it for a long time now, but in the beginning, we were not able to chat at all.
We have grown up to this point, and I still have a lot of work to do, but I would like to thank the staff of Harugetsu and all the listeners for helping us to grow up to this point.
I am so grateful to the staff and listeners of Harugetsu for helping us grow to this point.
And today is, you know...
Today is the release day of "Cute Memorial.
Thank you so much for all the excitement on SNS!
All the songs are full of great songs,
I hope you will listen to not only the title song but also the coupling songs.
By the way, what do you think is my favorite song?
I like "Kimi to Seishun" the best, but all the songs are good, so please listen to them.
Thank you very much for coming to see me today.
Yes, thank you all for coming to see me today, and thank you also to those of you who are watching the broadcast.
I've been a guest and personality on Radio Japan's "Sunny and Sometimes Super Tokimeki Propaganda Club" and "60 Tribe,
I'm also a guest and personality at 60 Tribe, and I've been working on an English movie in Nagano, Japan,
I don't know, I've been a part of it since I was a little girl,
Even before this "Hareki Jikan" was established, I had my own corner in 60 Tribe,
We were able to do a public recording at Radio Japan, a station that has been a great help to us, and we were able to do a radio show on the important day of our release.
Radio Japan lent us their support on the important day of the release.
Radio Japan lent us their support on the big day of the release and gave us a place to do a public recording like this.
I am very happy that we were able to celebrate the release day together with the members of the publicity department. After the Corona disaster, we were not able to hold the release event,
I think there were a lot of things that happened,
I am very happy to have been able to do so little by little,
I am very happy that we are now able to do so little by little.
I am also very happy to be able to meet with everyone at Radio Nippon, which has helped me a lot,
I am also very happy to be able to meet you all like this.
And I'm also very happy to be able to meet with everyone here at Radio Nippon, which has been very kind to us.
I'm very happy that we have good songs coming to us again.
I'm very happy that these good songs are coming to us again, and I'm looking forward to performing them at the live.
I'm really looking forward to performing them at the concert.
I'm really looking forward to the live performance.
I'm really looking forward to seeing them at the concert.
You can tell me who was who, who was who, who was who on the posters, etc.
I saw that you were excited with X and so on, so I was very happy to see that too.
So I was really happy to see that.
And as Jillia mentioned, there are going to be some benefit events in the near future.
I hope that we can continue to make many more of these cute memorials.
I would be happy if everyone's everyday life with super-time warfare becomes a day of cute memorials.
Please keep up the good work. Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you all very much for today. Thank you very much for the delivery. I love Harujiki so much, and I love talking on the radio with the members like this,
I love talking on the radio with everyone and the members, and also connecting with fans through e-mails,
I love talking with the members on the radio, and I also love getting e-mails from fans and connecting with the members,
I think it is a very important place for us,
This is the first time for you to do a public recording?
I am so happy to be able to do this first public recording of "Atchulik",
I was able to hold an open recording of Achurik for the first time, and many people nodded their heads every time I said a word,
I feel so warmed by the nodding of their heads every time I say a word.
Thank you for all your help.
Today is the day, as everyone has been saying,
It's the release day of the cute memorial,
Thank you very much. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I hope that we will become even more famous in the future, and that the day will come when everyone will be filled with smiles,
I hope that we can make you smile even more in the days to come.
I will do my best so that everyone will like us even more and more.
Thank you for your continued support.
So, to those of you who are watching the broadcast, and to those of you who are in the audience, thank you very much for coming today.
Did you all have a good time?
Thank you very much. It's been about 6 years since we started broadcasting "Sunny Time",
This is a very long-running program.
I have been broadcasting since I was a little girl, and I don't even know what I'm talking about,
I am sure there may be some that I didn't know what they were talking about since I was really little,
But you did not give up on us, and you will continue to do so now and in the future,
But they did not give up on us, and they will not give up on us now and in the future.
I feel really happy that you have allowed us to continue our program like this.
And I'm really happy to be able to hear directly from you through your e-mails and so on.
I think it takes a lot of courage to send an e-mail.
It takes a lot of courage to send an e-mail, but it's also good to read it and let it soak into us,
I think it's one of the great things about radio, to be able to put them on the air and have people listen to them,
If you come to a live concert and have a good time, please send us many more e-mails, and if we can share them with everyone, I think it will make it even more exciting,
I think this is a place that we would like to keep on making more and more important,
I was able to think again today that this is a place that I would like to cherish more and more in the future.
And here it is.
Today is also an important release day,
The visual on the poster is so cool!
I like it so much that I said, "Cool!
Isn't it cute?
Thank you very much.
It's a cute memorial, after all,
I wanted to be cute as well.
I really wanted to be cute.
I hope that the word "cute" will become a universal word.
It's the same with "like.
Now that the word "like" has spread
Next, I'd like to use the word "kawaii".
When the word "cute" comes to mind
I'd like to make the world that much cuter.
We would like to make the world that much cuter.
We're going to continue to make a lot of cute memorials, and we're also going to continue to make the inside coupling songs
I hope that everyone will love the cute memorial and the coupling songs in the album together.
So, I'm glad we could have a good time together today.
We will continue to make it more exciting in the spring time as well, so please give us your support.
Thank you very much.
Hey, everyone, please send me lots of e-mails.
I'm looking forward to receiving your e-mails!
Thank you very much for today's open recording. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. So, today's open recording will be aired on October 7, 14 at 1:00 a.m. on "Hareware Toki Chotokimeki Propaganda Club," so please check it out.
Please check it out.
And finally, I have one more announcement.
What, what, what, what?
Radio Japan's 65th anniversary timetable will be featured on the cover of the autumn/winter issue of "Chotoki Meki Propaganda Club.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
By the way, the cover & interview will also be published.
We did it just now, didn't we?
Interview.
I was introduced in the magazine,
And as for when and where it will be distributed,
Radio Japan's official website,
We will announce the distribution date and location on our website and in the program X, so please look forward to it.
I am sure that the booklet that you have today will be super-timed.
I am very happy.
I am really grateful to Radio Nippon for all the support they have given me,
Thank you very much.
I am very happy to be able to do so.
We will do our best to make Harujiki a program that will be loved for a long, long time,
So please listen to it a lot. Please listen to it a lot.
Thank you very much.
So, tomorrow, I will be with Kanami Tsujino, Anjulia, Hitaka Sakai, Haruka Izumi, and Ayaki Suda.
Haruka Izumi, Ayaki Suda, and Hiyori Yoshikawa.
That's all for us, the super-toki-meki young men's club!
Bye bye!
Thank you for the stream!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
See you soon!
Thank you! Thank you very much!